# Nagaraj S O Featured

Software Engineer seeking assignment in Software Development, Software Application Development, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Software Design, Program Management, Eclipse, Putty, WinSCP, Filezilla, eJira, Oracle, JavaScript, Typescript, Tortoise SVN



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 7 Month(s)

Current Company: Syniverse Technologies Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Putty, WinSCP, Filezilla, e Jira, JavaScript, Typescript, Tortoise SVN, angular, Core

Java, Eclipse, Software Developer, Bootstrap, CSS, UI Development, Javascript, HTML, Node. Js

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

### Summary

4.7 Years of experience as Software Developer in Software Design, analysis, development and implementation of web applications using Angularis and Angular.

Work experience in application development using with Angularjs, Angular, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and gulp.

Good knowledge on third party libraries HighCharts, underscorejs.

Aware of eJira scrum management tool.

Experience in Tortoise SVN, Putty, Filezilla and WinSCP.

Ability to learn & develop using new technologies quickly.

## **Work Experience**

#### Syniverse Technologies as Software Engineer

Feb 2019 to Till Date

Product: Symphony

Technical environment: AngularJS, JavaScript, Angular 4, Typescript, HTML, CSS with Agile Methodology, Spring boot,

Oracle 11g. Description:

This system will keep track of Roaming agreements and tariffs.

If agreements or tariffs are expiring in near term it will trigger an alert.

Reporting based on customer usage.

Responsibilities:

Involved in Requirement gathering and design document.

Developed agreement pages using Angular, HTML, CSS.

Involved in the development of the REST APIs using Spring Boot

#### ConnectM Technology Solutions as Software Engineer

Mar 2016 to Feb 2019

Project 1:

Client: Bharat Light and Power March 2016- February 2019

Technical environment: Angularjs, Angular 2, JavaScript, HTML, Bootstrap and CSS

Description:

The system is mainly designed for Renewable Energy Company and aimed to provide total information about wind mills and solar panels.

Power generation, wind speed, status of the respective wind mills. For solar assets irradiation and Status reports.

Reporting based on live data and Historic Data.

Responsibilities:

Involved in Requirement gathering and design document.

Developed web forms in Angular, HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

Developed reports for various time zones.

Developed master pages.

Project 2:

Client: Ashok Leyland (iAlert) June 2016- February 2019

Technical environment: Springs, AngularJS, JavaScript, HTML, CSS with Agile Methodology

Description:

The system is mainly designed for vehicle GPS tracking and aimed to provide status of the vehicle and nearest service centers.

Status of the respective Vehicles and Reporting using Charts

Reporting based on live data as well as Historic data.

Responsibilities:

Involved in Requirement gathering and design document.

Developed web forms in AngularJS, HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

Developed accordion control with Data List controls.

Developed master pages.

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science) from M.S Ramaiah Institute of Technology, affiliated to V.T.U. in 2015

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
JAVA	
JavaScript, TypeScript	
ORACLE 11G	
MS-Office:2010, Eclipse, Putty	
WinSCP, Filezilla, eJira	
Tortoise SVN	

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
kannada	Proficient			
Telugu	Beginner			

#### **Affirmative Action**

#### **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time